{
    "id": "393ce39d97a9401d9202c59e3a59358e",
    "title": "If And Unless Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. you eat too much, you will fall ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a9de48ddb1c491b89ef4b82a4aec771"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he doesn’t mend his ways, he will lose his job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4d8742853bd4d58b4c117f6d5c2de26"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… you don’t stop smoking, you will fall seriously ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "250ecde1001b425f8851fa469be0ca35"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t have won ……………….. he hadn’t helped me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d952c58eb7b4925824c7a3fe65ba22c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… he mends his ways, he will land in serious trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "886869330ebf41f58058ff932ad94045"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will take the job ………………… the pay is too low.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e0abe8f755b4defa50c4b62100a189a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be back tomorrow ………………… there is a train strike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a5baf6f414a4714890ba37ba6fbd8d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will quit my job ……………….. they don’t offer me a raise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5e70a8c6604c4732862553ce2d952d67"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be surprised …………………. she doesn’t recognize me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46b05754734b4f7a9d535b3315b24e35"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will look prettier ……………….. you don’t wear so much make-up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4a6cf41ebbd4cadb6429338d735fe76"
        }
    ]
}